# MUHAMMAD ALIUDDIN B. REFAK'AEI

Bachelor of Computer Science with Honours

## PERSONAL INFO

Name : Muhammad Aliuddin Bin Refak'aei

Date of Birth : 15/03/1997 Phone Number : 017 772 4897 Website : mdaliuddin.com E-mail : hello@mdaliuddin.com

Address : Taman Kota Masai, Pasir Gudang, Johor

LinkedIn Profile : Link Github Repo. : Link

#### **PROFILE**

I possess a strong knowledge in computer science fundamentals and specialises in web application development. I strive to provide results and solutions when presented with a task while demonstrating a high degree of professionalism. I aim to use systematic solutions in order to increase efficiency and overall productivity.

## **EDUCATION INFO**

2016 - present **Bachelor of Computer Science with Honours** 

Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia, Bangi

Relevant courses: Web Programming, Advance Database, Paradigm Programming, Network Programming, Introduction to Al

2015 - 2016 Foundation in Science

Universiti Teknologi Mara, Dengkil

Foundation studies in Physics, Mathematics, Chemistry and Biology

**MUET Band 5** 

2013 - 2014 Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)

SMK Taman Nusa Damai, Pasir Gudang

Perfect attendance award 2014

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Internship 15/07/2019 -31/12/2019

Orange Media Malaysia, Johor

- Developed and maintained annual event website and promotions
- Attended weekly development meeting

## **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

2016 - 2019 Vice President & Treasurer, MAD Club

Mobile Application Development Club

- Organize mobile application workshops for Higher Education and High School students
- Managed the treasury of over 30 members

2013 - 2015 Librarian

SMK Taman Nusa Damai

Maintained school library weekly

President, English Club

SMK Taman Nusa Damai English Club

Organize weekly English enhancement programs

President, Police Cadet

SMK Taman Nusa Damai Police Cadet

• Trained Police Cadets for yearly marching drills

## **RELEVANT SKILLS**

Programming : HTML/CSS, Python, JavaScript, Java, C#, PHP

Languages

Development Software : Git, SASS, Bootstrap3, Linux OS, Android Studio, Visual Code,

Languages : English & Bahasa Melayu

Driver's License : D

## INTEREST & ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Analog Photography Online Web Profile Travelling

- I enjoy using analog cameras for nature and street photography
- Currently developing my online profile website
- Have visited several countries across Asia